--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://www.hdcmct.com
影片压制: 暮雨潇潇   招募Q号: 76846146
洛杉矶 公元2029年
那些机器从核子战火的废墟中崛起
它们灭绝人类的战争肆虐了数十年
但最后的一场仗不会在未来发生
它会发生在这里 就是现在
就在今晚...
终  结  者
洛杉矶 公元1984年 凌晨1点52分
怎么回事?
What the hell?
狗娘养的王八蛋
Goddamn son of a bitch.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
嗨 轮到我了
Hey, my turn!
到我
Me.
来吧
Come on.
嗨 我该不是眼花看错了吧?
What's wrong with this picture?
夜色好出来散步?
Nice night for a walk?
夜色好出来散步
Nice night for a walk.
明天是洗衣日
Washday tomorrow.
没干净衣服穿 对吗?
Nothing clean, right?
没干净衣服穿 对
Nothing clean. Right.
我猜这家伙一定是喝了两箱六支装烈酒
I think this guy's a couple cans short of a six-pack.
你的衣服
Your clothes.
把衣服给我 马上
Give them to me...now.
去你的 混蛋
Fuck you, asshole!
嗨 甜心 怎么样?
Hey, sugar, how about it?
我不必忍受那个贱人的 伙计
I don't have to put up with that bullshit, man.
她老是缠着我
She's always after me.
我没有...我没有...
I don't...I don't...
嗨 老兄 你刚刚有没有见到一道强光?
Hey, buddy, did you just see a real bright light?
看到那家伙吗?
He the guy?
- 站住别动 - 他在逃跑
- Hold it right there! - He's rabbiting.
嗨 我叫你别动
Hey! I said hold it!
去吧
Go!
那个狗娘养的抢了我的裤子
That son of a bitch took my pants!
今天是什么日子? 日期!
What day is it? The date!
5月12号 星期四
The 12th of May. Thursday.
- 什么年份? - 什么?
- What year? - What?
他抢了我的枪 快追
He's got my gun! Let's go!
3831 他们把疑犯追丢了
3831, they lost the suspect.
莎拉康纳
Connor Sarah
大块头 替我守着它
Guard it for me, big buns.
你好 我迟到了
I'm late.
我也是
So am I.
莎拉康纳
Connor Sarah
- 开工了 - 我也是
- I'm in it. - So am I.
小姐 请给我一杯咖啡 好吗?
Honey, could I have that coffee now, please?
好的
Yes, sir.
牛排是谁点的?
Who gets the burly beef?
我点了烤牛肉
I ordered barbecued beef.
我想这是我的 但是我没有点薯条
I think that's mine, but I didn't order fries.
他点了烤牛肉 而我点的是豪华干椒牛肉
He gets the barbecued beef. Mine's the chili beef deluxe.
那是谁点的牛排?
Who gets the burly beef?
小姐? 我们想点菜
Miss, we're ready to order now.
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
哦 老天
Oh, lord.
这不是真皮 对吧?
This isn't real leather, is it?
这可不是一般的烂
This special sucks.
孩子 做得好 我该把小费给你
Nice going, kid. Ought to give you the tip.
要这样想 一百年后谁会在乎?
Look, in a hundred years, who's going to care?
阿莱姆体育用品枪械店
那支12口径半自动步枪
The 12-gauge auto-loader.
意大利制造
That's Italian.
你可以选择手动或自动
You can go pump or auto.
点45口径滑动式 配镭射瞄准器
The.45 long slide, with laser sighting.
它是全新的 我们刚进货
These are brand-new. We just got them in.
是一支好枪
That's a good gun.
只要扣下扳机 雷射光会发出
Just touch the trigger, the beam comes on...
然后你只要把红光对准你想射的地方就行了
and you put the red dot where you want the bullet to go.
百发百中
You can't miss.
还有什么需要?
Anything else?
一支40瓦的同步等离子步枪
A phased plasma rifle in the 40-watt range.
我们有的都摆出来了 老友
Just what you see, pal.
那支9毫米的乌兹型
The Uzi 9mm.
你很熟识枪械 老兄
You know your weapons, buddy.
任何一支都很适合家居防卫
Any one of these is ideal for home defense.
那么...要哪一支呢?
So which will it be?
全部
All.
今天我可以提早休市了
I may close early today.
手枪要等15天才有货
There's a fifteen-day wait on the handguns...
不过你现在就可以拿走那些步枪
but the rifles you can take right now.
- 你不能这样做 - 错
- You can't do that. - Wrong.
你好 宝贝 是我
Hi, baby. Yeah, it's me.
听着 我要你开车来接我
Listen, I need you to come pick me up.
我的摩托车出故障了
My bike just broke down.
我不管你在做什么 快来接我 什么鸟...
I don't care what you're doing. Come and get me. What the...
伙计 你的态度很有问题
Hey, man, you got a serious attitude problem.
莫特 你在哪里?
别这样 你在做什么?
莎拉康纳
Connor Sarah
莎拉康纳?
Sarah Connor?
是的
Yes
我在休息 卡拉正顶我的班
I'm on my break, Chuck. Carla's got my station.
莎拉 过来 这算是跟你有关
Sarah, come here! It's about you. Sort of.
这太不可思议了 你不会相信的
It's so incredible. You're not gonna believe this.
坐下 你会喜欢这个的
Sit down. You are going to love this.
什么?
What?
根据几名目击者的说法
...has been compiled from several witnesses.
重复: 莎拉康纳 35岁 有两名子女
Once again, Sarah Connor, thirty-five, mother of two...
今天下午在家里被残忍射杀
brutally shot to death in her home this afternoon.
你完蛋了 亲爱的
You're dead, honey.
如果你喜欢音响 最佳的音响
if you're into sound,for the greatest sound around,
就是鲍博立体声
come to Bob's Stereo at 2500 Sepulveda.
我们有低音喇叭 高频喇叭数码扬声器和镭射唱片
We've got woofers, tweeters, the newest in audio and compact discs.
还有图表均衡器和音响平衡器...
We've got graphic equalisers and sound balancers that...
对不起
Sorry.
你好
Hello?
首先 我会一个一个的解开你的上衣钮扣
First, I'm gonna rip the buttons off your blouse one by one...
然后用我的舌头从你的脖子...
and then run my tongue down your neck...
一路舔到你赤裸的乳房
to your bare, gleaming breasts...
然后 慢慢地...
and then slowly...
一寸一寸地慢慢脱掉你的牛仔裤
slowly pull your jeans off, inch by inch.
金珍 是麦特
Ginger, it's Matt!
然后一圈一圈地舔你的肚皮 逐渐往下去
And lick your belly in circles, further and further down...
然后用我的牙齿咬掉你的内裤
and then pull your panties off with my teeth.
你是谁?
Who is this?
天啊 莎拉?
God. Sarah?
我的天 对不起 我以为你是...
Oh, Jesus. I'm sorry. I thought you were...
我想找金珍 谢谢
Can I talk to Ginger, please?
好的 老友
Sure, Bunky.
是那个变态鬼
It's the creep.
首先 我会一个一个的解开你的上衣钮扣
First, I'm gonna rip the buttons off your blouse one by one...
冷静点 你们这帮该死的混蛋！
You fucking pigs!
你们等着瞧 我迟早干掉你们
Wait till I get my hands on you!
- 放开我! - 坐下 王八蛋
- Get off of me! - Sit down, fella.
艾德
Ed
- 搞到什么了? - 一条女尸
- What do you got? - Dead girl.
看得出来
I can see that.
莎拉·安·康纳 秘书 35岁
Sarah Ann Connor, secretary, thirty-five...
身中六枪 射击距离少于10英尺
shot six times at less than ten feet.
大口径的武器
Large caliber weapon.
废话 这些眼见功夫
You know, these work.
这是什么?
What's this?
又一条女尸 今天下午山谷分局送过来的
Dead girl two, sent over from Valley division this afternoon.
我肯定这些命案是有关联的
I'm sure there's a point to all of this.
看看死者的名字 艾德
Look at the name, Ed.
莎拉·路易斯·康纳 没弄错吧?
Sarah Louise Connor. Is this right?
你在开玩笑
You're kidding me.
报纸会对这个大做文章的
The press is going to be short-stroking it all over.
一个在一天内有特定模式的凶手
A one-day pattern killer.
我讨厌怪诞的杀手
I hate the weird ones.
那么?
So?
比普通人应得的更好
Better than mortal man deserves.
金珍 你有没有见到宝斯利？
Ginger, have you seen Pugsley?
最近没有 你查过留言了吗?
No, not lately. Did you check messages?
我以为你查过了
I thought you did.
莎拉 我是老妈
Hi, Sarah, this is your mom...
你在这里哪 小可爱
There you are, young man.
你挂念你妈妈
You mind your mother.
莎拉 我是史丹·莫斯基
Hi, Sarah. Dan Moorski.
有突发事件 今晚我不能应约了
Something's come up. I can't make it tonight.
我不能丢下不管那事
Just can't get out of it.
你看 真的很抱歉 我会补偿你的
Look, I'm really sorry. I'll make it up to you.
大约一天后再找你吧? 对不起 再见
Call you in a day or so, OK? Sorry. Bye.
那个混蛋 就算他有辆宝时捷又会怎样?
That bum. So what if he has a Porsche?
他不可以这样对待你的
He can't treat you like this.
今晚是小周末! 老天在上!
It's Friday night, for Christ's sake!
我没事的
I'll live.
我会打碎他的膝盖
I'll break his kneecaps.
宝斯利仍然爱我 是吗 宝贝?
Well, Pugsley still loves me, don't you, baby?
天 真恶心
God. It's disgusting.
我去看电影 老姐 你和麦特玩得开心点
I'm gonna go to a movie, kiddo. You and Matt have a good time
- 我们会的 你也是 - 好的
- We will. You, too. - OK.
该死的 麦特
Damn it, Matt!
该死
Oh, shit.
中尉 你们有没有察觉这两宗谋杀案...
Lieutenant, are you aware that these two killings...
发生的顺序和受害者
occurred in the same order...
在电话簿里的名字排列顺序是一样的?
as their listings in the phone book?
我能对你们这群家伙说什么? 无可奉告
Now, what can I tell you guys? No comment.
但是发生了两宗谋杀案件...
But we've got two murders...
那杯咖啡凉了两小时了
That coffee's two hours cold.
我还用它来弄熄香烟呢
I put a cigarette out in it.
你联系到下一名女子了吗?
Did you reach the next girl yet?
我一直只听到电话留言
No. I keep getting an answering machine.
- 派一组人去 - 我已经派了
- Send a unit. - I sent a unit.
没有人应门 那个经理还没有回家
There's no answer at the door, and the manager's not home.
- 打电话给她 - 我刚刚才打了
- Call her. - I just called her.
继续打给她
Call her again.
给我一支香烟
Give me a cigarette.
你好
Hi there.
捉弄到你了
Fooled you.
你在跟留言机谈话 但别害羞 没事的
You're talking to a machine, but don't be shy, it's OK.
留言机也需要爱 跟它谈谈吧
Machines need love, too, so talk to it.
同样的废话
Same shit.
我能听得到
I can hear it now.
他就要被叫成该死的"电话薄杀手"了
He's going to be called the goddamn "Phone Book Killer."
我讨厌这些报界触目的案件
I hate these press cases.
特别是变态的触目案件
Especially the weird press cases.
- 你去哪里? - 去发个声明
- Where you going? - To make a statement.
也许能让这帮走狗换换花样为我们工作
Maybe make these jackals work for us for a change.
如果我能够在11点前上了电视...
If I can get on the tube by eleven o'clock...
或者她会打电话给我们
maybe she'll call us.
我看起来怎样?
Well, how do I look?
像堆屎 老板
Like shit, boss.
去你妈的
Your mama.
中尉!
Lieutenant!
刚收到消息
This just in.
警方已经宣布了第二名死者的姓名
Police have announced the name of the victim...
是今天发生的命案
in the second of two execution-style murders...
很奇怪 两名死者都是同名同姓
which took place today.
两名受害者的名字都差不多
The names of the two victims are virtually identical.
两小时前 35岁的莎拉·安·康纳...
Two hours ago, 35-year-old Sarah Ann Connor...
被发现死在寓所里
was pronounced dead at the scene in her Santa Monica apartment...
-换个台好吗?  -莎拉·路易斯·康纳
-Can we change this?  -Sarah Louise Connor was slain...
别碰它
Don't touch it!
在今天早些时候也于家中被杀
...earlier today in her home.
而警方拒绝猜测...
Now, police are refusing to speculate...
这两宗凶杀案中显而易见的相似点
on the apparent similarity between these shooting deaths...
现在已经证实两名受害者之间
and no other connection between the two victims...
再没有其他关联
has been established as of yet.
我们会随时为大家报导最新消息
We'll have more on this story as it comes in.
一场惊人的大火由于得到溶剂 石油...
A spectacular fire fueled by solvents, oils...
和其他易燃性液体的相助...
and other flammable liquids...
席卷了北春天大街上的一间石油公司
swept through an oil company on North Spring Street...
这场大火是周三晚在唐人街东北处燃起的
just northeast of Chinatown Wednesday night.
莎拉康纳
Connor Sarah
黑科技酒吧
- 这里有电话? - 在后面有!
- Hey, you got a phone? - It's in the back!
四块半
Hey! Four-fifty.
你已接通洛杉矶警局
This is the Los Angeles Police Department emergency number.
紧急热线
Emergency number.
我们的所有线路都正忙
All our lines are busy.
如果你需要召警车支援 请别挂断
If you need a police car sent, please stay on the line.
巡逻中的2-11小队...
Two-eleven in progress...
在第三街与奥林匹克街交界的鲍勃酒吧附近有状况
corner of Third and Cameron.
继续啊
Go on.
我会用你来制皮带
I'm going to make a belt out of you.
别逼我打爆你的头 伙计
Don't make me bust you up, man!
你好 捉弄到你了
Hi there. Fooled you.
你在跟留言机谈话 但别害羞 没事的
You're talking to a machine, but don't be shy, it's OK.
留言机也需要爱 跟它谈谈吧
Machines need love, too, so talk to it...
金珍..就是我..或者莎拉会回复你的
and, Ginger, that's me, or Sarah will get back to you.
请等候"咇"的一声
Wait for the beep.
金珍 我是莎拉 要是在家你快点接电话
Ginger, this is Sarah! Pick up if you're there!
我在比科大道的黑科技酒吧
I'm at this place on Pico Boulevard called Technoir.
我真的很害怕
I'm really scared.
我想有人在跟踪我
I think that there's somebody's after me.
我希望你很快听到这个留言
I hope that you play this back soon.
我要你和麦特尽快来接我
I need you and Matt to come and pick me up as soon as possible.
警方一直在转接我的电话
The police keep transferring me around.
我会再试试打给他们的
I'm gonna give them another try.
这里的号码是555-9175
The number here is 555-9175.
回我电话 老姐 我需要你的帮忙
Call me, kiddo. I need your help.
莎拉康纳
Connor Sarah
是她
It's her.
莎拉康纳？ 我是特斯勒警长
Sarah Connor? It's Lieutenant Traxler.
警长 别要我等或者转线!
Lieutenant, don't put me on hold or transfer me!
我不会 请放松点 你在哪里?
I won't. Just relax. Can you tell me where are you?
在一间叫做黑科技的酒吧里
I'm in this bar called Technoir.
我知道 在比科大道 你没事吧?
I know. It's on Pico. Are you all right?
但我不想离开
Yeah, but I don't want to leave.
我认为有个家伙在跟踪我
I think there's a guy following me.
好吧 现在听着 康纳小姐
All right, now listen, Miss Connor.
你仔细听好 你正在一个公众场所
Now listen carefully. You're in a public place...
所以我们赶到之前你都会安全的 只要你留在原地
so you'll be safe till we get there, but stay visible.
别去外面 甚至连洗手间也别去
Don't go outside or even to the rest room.
几分钟内我们就会赶到
I'll have a car there in a hot minute.
那个家伙没有付钱
Hey, that guy didn't pay.
你想活命就跟着我走
Come with me if you want to live.
快点
Come on!
我是1-L19 我发现有人肇事后逃跑
This is 1-L19. I got a hit-and-run felony.
可疑车辆是新型灰色福特
Suspect vehicle...late model gray Ford...
在第七街向西逃走
headed westbound on Seventh.
他开得很快 一路狂打灯
He's really moving, punching lights all the way.
马上派救护车
I'm going to need an ambulance...
来第七街和百老汇街交界处
at Seventh and Broadway right now.
别动
Hold it!
所有单位留意一辆旧型灰色福特...
All units watch for a late-model gray Ford...
最后被发现在第七街和百老汇街交界向西行走
last seen westbound on Seventh and Broadway.
坐稳
Hold on.
你有没有受伤?
Are you injured?
你有没有中枪?
Are you shot?
完全按我说的去做
Do exactly what I say!
完全!
Exactly!
不能动除非我允许 不能发出声音除非我允许
Don't move unless I say. Don't make a sound unless I say.
明白吗?
Do you understand?
- 你明白吗? - 明白!
- Do you understand? - Yes! Yes!
求你别伤害我
Please, don't hurt me.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you.
我叫里斯 科技部队中士 编号BN38416
I'm Reese, Sergeant Techcom, BN38416...
受命来保护你
assigned to protect you.
你已经成为要被终结的目标
You've been targeted for termination.
嫌疑犯在国家街和奥林匹克街交界处 你尝试去拦截 1-L19
Attempt to intercept, 1-L19.
我是1-L19
This is 1-L19.
在奥林匹克街向西行即将到达奥佛兰道
Westbound on Olympic approaching Overland.
这一定是搞错了
This is a mistake.
我什么也没做过
I didn't do anything.
现在没有 但你会去做的
No, but you will.
你的生存是非常重要的事
It's very important that you live.
这不会是真的
This isn't true.
那个人怎么能站起来追你...
How could that man just get up after you...
它不是人 是台机器
He's not a man...a machine.
一台终结者 一台电脑动力系统101型号
A Terminator. A Cyberdyne Systems Model 101.
一台机器?
A machine?
就像机械人?
Like a robot?
不是机械人 是电脑人
Not a robot. A cyborg.
一台由电脑控制的有机体
A cybernetic organism.
- 他刚才在流血 - 等一下
- No. He was bleeding. - Just a second.
低下你的头
Get your head down!
好了 听着
All right, listen.
终结者是一个混合体
The Terminator's an infiltration unit...
半人半机械
part man, part machine.
里面是一个超合金的战斗骨架...
Underneath, it's a hyperalloy combat chassis...
微型处理器控制 全由钢板保护 非常牢固
microprocessor controlled, fully armored...very tough.
但外表是活人组织
But outside, it's living human tissue...
肌肉 皮肤 毛发 血液...都是为电脑人培植的
flesh, skin, hair, blood...grown for the cyborgs.
- 听着 我不知道什么...- 专心点!
- Look, I don't know what...- Pay attention!
我要丢弃这辆车
I got to ditch this car.
600系列是塑胶皮肤
The 600 series had rubber skin.
我们很容易认出来 但这批是新造的
We spotted them easy, but these are new.
它们很像人类
They look human...
流汗 口臭...所有事都一样
sweat, bad breath, everything.
很难辨认出来
Very hard to spot.
我不得不等到他走近你时才锁定他
I had to wait till he moved on you before I could zero him.
听着...
Look...
我不是傻子 你明白的
I am not stupid, you know.
他们还不能制造出像那样的东西
They cannot make things like that yet.
现在还不可以
Not yet.
40年后就可以了
Not for about forty years.
你是说它来自未来?
Are you saying it's from the future?
一个有可能的未来
One possible future.
依你看 我对科技一窍不通
From your point of view...I don't know tech stuff.
那么你也是来自未来 对吗?
Then you're from the future, too, is that right?
- 对 - 对
- Right. - Right.
电脑人感觉不到痛楚
Cyborgs don't feel pain.
我感觉得到 不要再那样做
I do. Don't do that again.
- 请放我走 - 听好并弄明白!
- Just let me go. - Listen and understand!
那个终结者就在外面
That Terminator is out there.
不可能跟它谈判
It can't be bargained with.
不可能跟它讲道理
It can't be reasoned with.
它不会感到同情或后悔或恐惧
It doesn't feel pity or remorse or fear.
它绝不会就此罢休! 永远不会
And it absolutely will not stop ever!
直到你死掉
Until you are dead.
你能制止它吗?
Can you stop it?
我不知道
I don't know.
靠这些武器 我不知道
With these weapons, I don't know.
所有单位 可疑车辆灰色福特被发现...
All units. Gray Ford suspect vehicle has been found...
在第四街和百老汇街交界的一个停车场里
in a parking structure at Fourth and Beaudry.
位置是下层
Location, lower level.
疑匪是个年约25岁 身高六尺 穿绿色外衣的白种男人
Suspect described as male, white, six feet, 25 years, green overcoat.
最后被发现在...
Last seen on....
里斯?
Reese?
为什么是我?
Why me?
它为什么要对付我?
Why does it want me?
发生了一场核战...
There was a nuclear war...
从现在起的数年后
a few years from now.
这里的一切...
All this...
这整个地方 所有的东西...
this whole place, everything...
都会消失
it's gone.
就此消失
Just gone.
有一些生还者
There were survivors.
这处 那处 散落各地
Here, there.
甚至没有人知道是谁发动了战争
Nobody even knew who started it.
是那些机器 莎拉
It was the machines, Sarah.
我不明白
I don't understand.
防卫网络电脑...
Defense network computers...
新型的 功能强大
New...powerful
接驳到所有的东西
Hooked into everything.
一切的运行都交给了它
Trusted to run it all.
他们说它变得聪明起来
They say it got smart...
智慧的一种新形态
a new order of intelligence.
接着它把所有人类视为威胁...
Then it saw all people as a threat...
而不把我们看成智慧的另一类
not just the ones on the other side.
它在刹那间决定了我们的命运
Decided our fate in a microsecond...
灭绝
extermination.
你可有目睹这场战争?
Did you see this war?
我在战后的废墟中长大
I grew up after it in the ruins...
挨饥抵饿 躲避那些HK们
starving, hiding from HKs.
- HK? - 追捕杀手
- HKs? - Hunter-Killers...
自动机械化工厂制造的巡逻机器
patrol machines built in automated factories.
我们大部分人被围捕
Most of us were rounded up...
关在拘留营里等候被逐一处置
put in camps for orderly disposal.
这是被雷射扫瞄器烙下的
This was burned in by laser scanner.
我们中的一些人得以活下来...
Some of us were kept alive...
负责...
to work...
搬运尸体
loading bodies.
那些处理部队日以继夜地运作
The disposal units ran night and day.
我们已接近于永恒的终结
We were that close to going out forever.
但是有一个人开始教我们反抗...
But there was one man who taught us to fight...
攻袭拘留营的线路
to storm the wire of the camps...
把那些他妈的金属混蛋砸了个稀巴烂
to smash those metal motherfuckers into junk.
他扭转了局势
He turned it around.
带领我们逃离了死亡边缘
He brought us back from the brink.
他的名字是康纳...
His name is Connor...
约翰康纳
John Connor
你的儿子 莎拉
Your son, Sarah.
你未出生的儿子
Your unborn son.
你来开车
Drive!
里斯
Reese!
不 里斯 不
No! Reese No!
- 他们会杀死你的 - 在凯迪拉克车里的人!
- They'll kill you. - You in the Cadillac!
马上举高双手让我们看见
Let me see your hands now!
下车
Get out of the car!
跪下
Drop to your knees!
下车
Out of the car.
跪下
Drop to the ground.
所有PC-207单位注意疑匪已被制伏
All units PC-207. Suspect is in custody.
取消进一步支援
Cancel further assistance.
莎拉...莎拉 尝一点这个吧
Sarah, try to drink some of this.
听着 你肯定是他们?
Listen, are you sure it's them?
我是说 也许我该看一下尸体
Maybe I should look at the bodies.
已经鉴定过他们的身份 毫无疑问
No. They've been identified. There's no doubt.
天哪!
Oh, God.
金珍
Ginger
小伙子
Bunky
莎拉
Sarah
莎拉 这是西伯曼医生
Sarah, this is Dr. Silberman.
莎拉 你好
Hi, Sarah.
我要你把里斯对你说的一切都告诉他
I want you to tell him everything Reese told you.
你觉得可以应付得来吗?
Do you feel up to that?
大概可以
I guess so.
你是个医生?
You're a doctor?
犯罪心理学医生
Criminal psychologist.
里斯是不是疯了?
Is Reese crazy?
这事就是我们将要查明的
That's what we're gonna find out.
这么说 你是个军人 你为谁而战呢?
So, you're a soldier, fighting for whom?
隶属第132团 由贝里率领
With the 132nd, under Perry.
由21年到27年
From 21 to 27.
那是2027年?
That's the year 2027?
没错 然后我被指派到...
That's right. And I was assigned...
真他妈妙极了
This is fucking great.
最后那两年直接受命于约翰康纳
...the last two years under John Connor.
敌人又是什么人?...
Who was the enemy again?
一个电脑防卫系统 制造来用于...
A computer defense system built for...
见鬼 抱歉
Damn. Sorry.
电脑动力系统替萨诺力制造的
Built for SAC-NORAD by Cyberdyne Systems.
我明白了
I see.
这台电脑认为只要杀了它
And this computer thinks it can win...
敌人的母亲就可以胜利
by killing the mother of its enemy.
实际上 可以算是在他受孕前就把他杀掉
Killing him, in effect, before he's even conceived...
一种倒逆的堕胎?
a sort of retroactive abortion?
西伯曼那家伙笑死我了
That guy Silberman cracks me up.
上周 有个家伙在这里气得他大发脾气
Last week, he had this guy in here that burned his Afghan.
先是冒烟 然后火气就爆发了
Screwed it first, then he set it on fire.
闭嘴
Shut up.
为什么电脑不直接杀死那时的康纳
Why didn't the computer just kill Connor then?
为什么会有这个煞费苦心的终结者计划?
Why this elaborate scheme with the Terminator?
它没有选择
It had no choice.
它们的防御网络被摧毁了
Their defense grid was smashed.
我们快赢了
We'd won.
杀掉那时的康纳也不会有何分别
Taking out Connor then would make no difference.
天网必须完全擦去他在历史中的存在
Skynet had to wipe out his entire existence.
是不是当你们占领了综合实验室时...
Is that when you captured the lab complex...
...找到的那个...叫什么来着?
and found that...What is it called?
时空转移装置?
The time displacement equipment?
没错 那个终结者已经被传送过来了
That's right. The Terminator had already gone through.
康纳派我来阻击它 然后他们把整个地方都炸毁了
Connor sent me to intercept, and they blew the whole place.
那你准备怎样回去?
How are you supposed get back?
我回不去了
I can't.
没有人可以回家
Nobody goes home.
没有别的人可以过来
Nobody else comes through.
就只有他...和我
It's just him...and me.
为什么你不带些武器来?
Why didn't you bring any weapons...
带些更先进的武器?
something more advanced?
你们没有镭射枪的吗?
Don't you have ray guns?
镭射枪
Ray guns.
给我看看一件未来的科技
Show me a piece of future technology.
你要光着身体
You go naked.
传送跟由生物体产生的磁场有关
Something about the field generated by a living organism.
- 无生命的东西是不能传送的 - 为什么?
- Nothing dead will go. - Why?
那鬼东西不是我制造的!
I didn't build the fucking thing!
但这个电脑人 它是不是金属...
OK. But this cyborg, if it's metal...
由活体组织包着的金属!
Surrounded by living tissue!
对 是的
Right.
这种说法可真妙
This is great stuff.
我可以用这家伙来赚钱
I could make a career out of this guy.
你看这一段话多么精明
You see how clever this part is?
完全不需要一点点的证据
How it doesn't require a shred of proof?
大多数偏执狂的妄想都很纷乱...
Most paranoid delusions are intricate...
但这个却很精明
but this is brilliant.
为什么另外那两个女人会被杀?
Why were the other two women killed?
大部分记录都在战争中遗失了
Most of the records were lost in the war.
天网对约翰康纳的母亲几乎一无所知
Skynet knew almost nothing about Connor's mother.
她的全名 她住在哪里 他们只知道她所在的城市
Her full name, where she lived. They just knew the city.
终结者只是按计划好的来做
The Terminator was just being systematic.
我们回过头谈谈...
Well, let's go back to...
听着 你已经听够了 我已经回答了你的问题
Look, you have heard enough! I have answered your questions!
现在我要见莎拉康纳
Now I have to see Sarah Connor!
恐怕轮不到我来作主
I'm afraid that's not up to me.
那我为什么要跟你说话?
Then why am I talking to you?
因为我可以帮助你
Because I can help you.
- 谁是这里的负责人? 收声! - 求你
- Who is in authority here? Shut up! - Please
你还是不明白 对不对?
You still don't get it, do you?
他会找到她的
He'll find her.
那是他要做的
That's what he does!
他只会这样做
That's all he does!
你无法制止他的
You can't stop him!
他会宰了你 砍断她的喉咙...
He'll wade through you, reach down her throat...
挖出她那见鬼的心脏!
and pull her fucking heart out!
医生
Doc.
放开我...
Let go of me...
对不起
Sorry.
那么 里斯是疯子?
So, Reese is crazy?
用专门的术语来说...他是个无赖
In technical terminology...he's a loon.
莎拉 这是他们所谓的身体护甲
Sarah, this is what they call body armor.
我们的特种部队都穿着这个
Our TAC guys wear these.
它能挡住12口径的子弹
It'll stop a 12-gauge round.
另外那个家伙一定是在他外套下面穿了一件
This other individual must have worn one under his coat.
触摸一下 来吧
Feel that. Go ahead.
当时他用手击穿了挡风玻璃又如何解释?
What about when he punched through the windshield?
他很可能服食了麻醉药
He was probably on PCP.
就算他的手每根骨头都断了 几小时内也感觉不到的
Broke every bone in his hand and wouldn't feel it for hours.
曾经有个家伙...看见这疤痕吗?
There was this guy once...See this scar?
- 拿着 - 谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
另一个房间里有一张沙发
There's a couch in this other room.
为什么你不去躺一下 并试试看能不能睡一小会呢?
Why don't you stretch out and try to get some sleep?
要一个小时你母亲才能从大熊镇来到这里
It'll be an hour before your mother gets here from Big Bear.
- 我睡不着 - 尽量试试
- I can't sleep. - Try.
那张沙发看起来不怎么样 但睡起来很舒服
It may not look it, but that couch is very comfortable.
你会绝对安全的
You'll be perfectly safe.
我们在这座大厦里有30个警员
We got 30 cops in this building.
谢谢你
Thank you.
晚安
Good night.
我是莎拉康纳的一个朋友
I'm a friend of Sarah Connor.
我被告知她在这里 请问我能见她吗?
I was told that she's here. Could I see her, please?
你不能见她 她正在录口供
No. You can't see her. She's making a statement.
她在哪里?
Where is she?
还要好一会儿
Look, it may take a while.
你要等的话 那边有张长椅
If you want to wait, there's a bench over there.
我等下回来
I'll be back.
那究竟是什么声音?
What the hell was that?
有枪击!
Gunshot!
那是什么? 恐怖分子吗?
What is it, terrorists?
快走! 快走!
Let's go! Let's go!
留在这里
Stay here.
我们快离开这里! 快来!
Let's get out of here! Come on!
他有一支自动式武器!
He's got an automatic weapon!
快点 快点
Move it, move it!
这些光管到底是怎么了?
What the hell happened to the lights?
看着他
Watch him.
自动式武器
Automatic weapons!
锁上并塞住! 我们快走!
Lock and load! Let's go!
开火! 开火!
Fire! Fire!
艾德
Ed
莎拉
Sarah
里斯
Reese
这边
This way.
新闻时间 4:36分
KFLB Newstime 4:36.
首先是重点新闻...燃料
In the top story of the hour...
加州有史以来最大型的
the largest single law enforcement mobilization...
一次执法行动正在展开
in California history is currently underway.
警方正在五个南部县区
Police in five southern counties...
进行一次大型搜捕...
are engaged in a massive manhunt for an unident...
拿着这个
Take this.
好了 我们来把这个推离公路
All right, let's get this off the road.
- 你冷吗? - 冻僵了
- You cold? - Freezing.
里斯
Reese...
你有首名吗?
You got a first name?
卡友
Kyle
Kyle...
在你穿越时空时它是什么样的?
what's it like when you go through time?
白光
White light.
痛楚
Pain.
或许就像出生时一样吧
It's like being born maybe.
天哪!
Oh, my God.
我刚才吃了一记
I caught one back there.
你是说你中枪了?
You mean you got shot?
不是很严重
It's not bad.
我们得送你到医生那里
We got to get you to a doctor.
没事的 算了吧
It's OK. Forget it.
你说什么? 算了? 你疯了吗?
What do you mean, forget it? Are you crazy?
脱下外套
Take this off.
老天
Jesus.
看 它穿透了皮肉
See, it passed right through the meat.
这会使我作呕
This is going to make me puke.
你能说点东西吗?
Would you talk about something?
说什么呢?
What?
不知道 什么也好 随便说吧
I don't know. Anything. Just talk.
跟我说说我的儿子
Tell me about my son.
他和我差不多高
He's about my height.
他有和你一样的眼睛
He has your eyes.
他是怎样的人?
What's he like?
你信任他
You trust him.
他有一种力量
He's got a strength.
我愿意为约翰康纳牺牲
I'd die for John Connor.
至少我现在知道该给他取什么名宇
Well...at least now I know what to name him.
我猜你不知道他父亲是谁吧...
I don't suppose you know who the father is...
好让我在遇上他时不会叫他滚开
so I won't tell him to get lost when I meet him.
约翰从来没有提起过他
John never said much about him.
我知道他在战前就死了...
I know he dies before the war...
等等!
Wait!
我不想知道
I don't want to know.
那么 是约翰派你来的?
So, was it John that sent you here?
是我自愿的
I volunteered.
为什么?
Why?
这是一个认识传奇人物的机会
It was a chance to meet the legend...
莎拉康纳
Sarah Connor.
她教她的儿子战斗 组织能力...
Taught her son to fight, organize...
从他小时候就筹划好
prepare from when he was a kid.
在战争开始前你就已经躲藏起来...
When you were in hiding before the war...
你用过去式说着一些
You're talking about things I haven't done yet...
我还没有做的事
in the past tense.
这会使我发疯的
It's driving me crazy.
你肯定你找对人了?
Are you sure you have the right person?
我很肯定
I'm sure.
得了吧
Come on.
我看起来像是未来的母亲吗?
Do I look like the mother of the future?
我坚强吗? 有组织能力吗?
Am I tough, organized?
我甚至不能使让自己收支平衡
I can't even balance my checkbook.
里斯 我没有要求这个荣誉
Look, Reese, I didn't ask for this honor...
也不想要它 一点都不想要!
and I don't want it! Any of it!
你儿子要我带给你一条口信
Your son gave me a message to give to you.
他要我背熟它
Made me memorize it.
"感谢你 莎拉 在黑暗年代的英勇"
Thank you, Sarah, for your courage through the dark years.
"关于你将要面对的事 我无法帮助你"
I can't help you with what you must soon face...
"只能告诉你未来不是必然"
except to say that the future is not set.
"你必须得比你自认为的要更坚强"
You must be stronger than you imagine you can be.
"你一定要活下去 否则我永不会存在"
You must survive, or I will never exist.
就是这样
That's all.
包扎得非常好
That's a good field dressing.
你喜欢吗?
You like it?
我第一次帮人包扎
It's my first.
睡一会吧 就快天亮了
Get some sleep. It will be light soon.
好的
OK.
再跟我讲多些
Talk to me some more.
讲些什么?
About what?
跟我讲讲你来的地方
Tell me about where you're from.
好的
All right.
你在白天躲藏起来...
You stay down by day...
但是在晚上你可以四处活动
but at night you can move around.
你仍然得小心翼翼因为追捕杀手会使用红外线
You still have to be careful because the HKs use infrared.
不过它们并不很聪明
But they're not too bright.
约翰教我们干掉它们的方法
John taught us ways to dust them.
就在那时候 渗透者开始出现了
That's when the infiltrators started to appear.
终结者是最新型...
The Terminators were the newest...
最难对付的
the worst.
它正以搜寻模式横穿你的防区
Traversing your sector in search mode.
在你营地以北750米
750 meters north of your position.
明白 以北750米
Understand. 750 meters north.
我们走吧
Let's go.
拦截 完毕
Intercept. Over.
别着急 完成你的扫荡
Take it easy. Finish your sweep.
他们是那个象限里的清扫小组
They are scavenger teams in that quadrant.
避免接触
Avoid contact.
重复一遍: 避免接触
Repeat, avoid contact.
我们迟些再干掉他们
We'll get them later.
收到 伊凯领队
Roger, Echo Leader.
第九防区 你们的情况怎样?
Sector niner, what's your status?
情况正常
Situation normal.
我们正在路上
We're coming in.
收到
Roger.
射击基地 你们的情况怎样? 完毕
Firebase, what's your status? Over.
里斯 编号BN384
Reese. BN384.
好的 让他进来
Right. Let him in.
有渗透者在商业大道上
Any infiltrators at the shopping mall?
没问题 已干掉他们了
No problem. They were clean.
我们的监察者有一只爪坏了 我们正结束巡逻 完毕
We're cutting short the patrol. Over.
收到 Yankee-1-7 你可以安全折返
Roger, Yankee-1-7. You are clear to return.
终结者!
Terminator!
我梦见一些狗
I was dreaming about dogs.
我们用它们来辨认终结者
We use them to spot Terminators.
你的世界非常恐怖
Your world is pretty terrifying.
老友 你里面有只死猫还是什么?
Buddy, you got a dead cat in there, or what?
可能的回应：是 不是或走开 去你的 混蛋
去你的 混蛋
Fuck you, asshole.
妈妈的小屋
大熊镇 555-9861 云杉路181号
该死的
God damn!
谢谢
Thank you.
迪基旅馆
这个够不够?
Is this enough?
太够了
Yeah, it's enough.
我都不想问你是从哪里得来的
I don't want to ask where you got it.
- 来了 - 我们要一个房间
- I'm coming. - We need a room.
- 好的 - 要有厨房
- All right. - With a kitchen.
有带厨房的房间吗?
Do you have one with a kitchen?
再不洗澡我就快死了
I am dying for a shower.
我们还得检查你的绷带
We should check your bandage, too.
稍后吧 我要出去买点必需品
Later. I'm going out for supplies.
拿着这个
Keep this.
我不能告诉你我在哪里 妈
No, I can't tell you where I am, Mom.
有人叫我不要说出来
I was told not to say.
亲爱的 我要知道在哪里可以找到你
Honey, I need to know where I can reach you.
你叫我像个逃犯般躲在小屋里
You tell me to hide up at the cabin like some fugitive...
而你却不愿告诉我发生了什么事?
and you won't tell me what's going on?
我很担心焦虑你 亲爱的
I am worried sick, dear.
好吧
OK.
这是电话号码 准备好了吗?
Here's the number. Ready?
说吧
Yes. Go ahead.
号码是408-555-1439
It's 408-555-1439.
九号房 记下了吗?
Room nine. Got it?
我记下了
I've got it.
我得挂线了
I've got to go.
很抱歉现在我不能跟你说更多的
I'm sorry I can't tell you more right now.
我爱你 妈
I love you, Mom.
我也爱你 小甜心
I love you, too, sweetheart.
- 这里是迪基旅馆 - 把你们的地址给我
- Tiki Motel. - Give me your address.
买到了什么?
What have we got?
樟脑丸...
Mothballs.
玉米糖浆
Corn syrup.
氨水
Ammonia.
晚餐吃什么?
What's for dinner?
塑料炸弹
Plastique.
听起来不错
That sounds good.
这是什么?
What is it?
可以说是硝化甘油
Nitroglycerin, basically.
这样会牢固一点
It's a bit more stable.
我小时候学过这样弄
I learned to make it when I was a kid.
得确保别沾到引线上
Make sure there's none on the threads.
就像这样
Like this.
把盖扭上拧紧
Screw the end cap on.
力度得非常轻
Very gently.
你一定有一个很有趣的童年
You must have had a fun childhood.
很好
That's good.
好吧 像这样做多六个
All right. Six more like that...
我得开始做信管
and I'll get started on the fuses.
他会找到我们的 对不对?
He'll find us, won't he?
可能吧
Probably.
这件事永远不会完结 对吗?
It'll never be over, will it?
看看我 我在颤抖
Look at me. I'm shaking.
好一个传奇人物?
Some legend, huh?
你一定很失望了
You must be pretty disappointed.
我没有失望
No. I'm not.
卡友
Kyle
你那个时代的女人...
The women in your time...
她们是怎样的?
what are they like?
是精锐的战士
Good fighters.
我不是那个意思
That's not what I meant.
有没有意中人?
Was there someone special?
意中人?
Someone?
一个姑娘 你明白
A girl. You know.
没有
No.
从来没有
Never.
从来没有?
Never?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
这么多痛苦
So much pain.
痛苦是可以抑制的
Pain can be controlled.
只要你不去想它
You just disconnect it.
那么你没有感觉?
So you feel nothing?
约翰康纳曾经给我一张你的照片
John Connor gave me a picture of you once.
当时我不明白为什么
I didn't know why at the time.
它很旧了
It was very old...
有点破烂
torn...
也褪色了
faded.
你当时很年轻 像现在一样
You were young like you are now.
只是你看起来有点悲伤
You seemed just a little sad.
我一直想知道那时候你在想着什么
I always wondered what you were thinking at that moment.
我谨记着每一条线...
I memorized every line...
每一条曲线
every curve.
我穿越了时空来找你 莎拉
I came across time for you, Sarah.
我爱你
I love you.
我一直爱着你
I always have.
我不该那样说的
I shouldn't have said that.
想快点
Think fast!
交换位置
Trade places!
快点 开快点
Faster! Drive faster!
卡友 天哪!
Kyle Oh, my God!
狗娘养的混蛋!
Son of a bitch!
你留在这里
You stay here.
我们快离开这里
Let's get out of here.
下车
Get out.
卡友 快点 出来
Kyle! Come on! Get up!
他就到了! 卡友!
He's coming! Kyle!
快点
Come on!
帮帮忙! 快走!
Help me! Get out!
快走
Get out!
快点
Come on!
Faster!
不要停 跑
Don't stop! Run!
莎拉
Sarah?
卡友
Kyle
我们成功了
We did it, Kyle.
We got it.
不
No.
等一会
Wait!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
掩饰 那样它就无法追踪我们
Cover...so he can't track us.
启动自动程序
快点
Come on!
不 卡友
No, Kyle!
来吧
Come on!
别管我
Leave me here.
快起来
Get up!
快走 里斯
Move it, Reese!
站起来 士兵
On your feet, soldier!
站起来 快走
On your feet! Move it!
后面 去后面
Back. Go back.
- 快逃 莎拉. - 不
- Run, Sarah. - No.
快跑
Run!
Run.
来吧 天杀的混蛋
Come on, motherfucker.
不...
No.
你要死翘翘了 混蛋
You're terminated, fucker.
卡友
Kyle
11月10日 第7卷
Tape 7, November 10.
我说到哪里?
Where was I?
对我来说 最难下决定的是...
What's most difficult for me is trying to decide...
哪些该告诉你 哪些不该
what to tell you and what not to.
不过我想在你成长到足以理解
But I guess I have a while yet...
这些带子之前我还有一段时间
before you're old enough to even understand these tapes.
现在 时间对我来说够多了
They're more for me at this point...
所以我可以慢慢想清楚
just so that I can get it straight.
加满它
Fill her up.
我应该告诉你关于你父亲的事吗?
Should I tell you about your father?
孩子 那是个难题
Boy, that's a tough one.
要是你知道了他是你父亲
Will it affect your decision to send him here...
会不会影响你派他来这里的决定?
knowing that he is your father?
如果你不派卡友来 就不会有你
If you don't send Kyle, you can never be.
老天 思考这种事会使人发疯的
God, a person could go crazy thinking about this.
我想我会告诉你
I suppose I will tell you.
这是我至少该做的
I owe him that.
要是你知道了以下的事也许会有帮助...
Maybe it'll help if...
在我们共度的短暂时光里...
you know that in the few hours that we had together...
我们相当于爱了一生一世
we loved a lifetime's worth.
他刚才说什么?
What did he just say?
他说你非常漂亮
He says you're very beautiful...
而且他对向你要五美元照相费
and he's ashamed to ask you...
感到不好意思
for five American dollars for his picture...
但如果他不向你要 他父亲就会打他
but if he doesn't, his father will beat him.
真会做生意 孩子
Pretty good hustle, kid.
他刚才说什么?
What did he just say?
他说有一场风暴就快来了
He said there's a storm coming in.
我知道
I know.